Inventory of the Francis P. Lee Papers 1727-1866
Earl Gregg Swem Library, College of William and Mary
- Sermons and Essays.
  - Francis P. Lee Sermon #298 "Lessons of Childhood," 1846 August 11 [sic]., 1 item. Ms. (Box-folder 10:16)
  - Francis P. Lee Sermon #299 "The Cross Our Glory," 1846 September 17., 1 item. Ms. (Box-folder 10:17)
  - Francis P. Lee Sermon #300 "Grounds of Despair and Hope," 1846 September 20., 1 item. Ms. (Box-folder 10:18)
  - Fra[nci]s P. Lee Sermon #301 "The Carnal Mind," 1846 September 30., 1 item. Ms. (Box-folder 10:19)
  - Francis P. Lee Sermon #302 "Danger of the Wicked," 1846 October 2., 1 item. Ms. (Box-folder 10:20)
  - Francis P. Lee Sermon #303 "Sin and Death," 1846 December 8., 1 item. Ms. (Box-folder 10:21)
  - Francis P. Lee Sermon #304 "2 Cor. 8: 12," 1847 January 8., 1 item. Ms. (Box-folder 10:22)
  - Francis P. Lee Sermon #305 "Put Ye on the Lord Jesus Christ," 1846[sic] [1847] January 16., 1 item. Ms. (Box-folder 10:23)
  - [Francis P. Lee] Sermon #306 "1. Cor. 4: 5," [1847, ca. January-March]., 1 item. Ms. (Box-folder 10:24)
  - [Francis P. Lee] Sermon #307 "Temperance," [1847, ca. January-March]., 1 item. Ms. (Box-folder 10:25)
  - [Francis P. Lee Sermon] #309 "Victory Over the World," 1847 April 10., 1 item. Ms. (Box-folder 10:26)
  - Francis P. Lee Sermon #310 The Expulsion," 1847 June 1., 1 item. Ms. (Box-folder 10:)
  - Francis P. Lee Sermon #311 "Ps. 14: 12," 1847 July 17., 1 item. Ms. (Box-folder 10:)
  - Francis P. Lee Sermon #312 "Gratitude to God," 1847 July 14., 1 item. Ms. (Box-folder 10:29)
  - Francis P. Lee Sermon #314 "Numbers 24: 23," 1847 August 12., 1 item. Ms. (Box-folder 10:30)
  - Francis P. Lee Sermon #315 "On Mark 4: 38," 1847 September 1., 1 item. Ms. (Box-folder 10:31)
  - [Francis P. Lee] Sermon "On John 3: 14, 15," 1847 n.d., 1 item. Ms. (Box-folder 10:32)
  - Sermon Fragments, 1847 n.d., 8 items. (Box-folder 10:33)